5210challenge.org 2017-08-14

# Privacy Policy | 5210 Challenge

_We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate 5210Challenge.org’s firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information._

## The use of Cookies

The 5210Challenge.org website uses cookies to enable users to navigate between pages within the 5210Challenge.org tracking pages and remain logged in as a member. Since much of the information displayed is according to user membership, this is a necessary component of our website. Here is a link to more information on how to enable cookies on your computer **if you are having difficulties with the site maintaining your login** status: <http://www.google.com/cookies.html>

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

The privacy of both visitor's and member’s information is important to us, and, simply put, we do not share any personal information with anyone, including businesses, organizations, schools, sponsors or third parties, unless a member has provided permission for us to do so.

Statistical aggregation of member’s point scores, number of entries, zip code, age, and BMI variance may be used to evaluate the success of 5210Challenge.org in promoting public health. This data will only be used for statistical analysis without reference to member’s name or user name.

## Disclosure Required by Law

5210Challenge.org may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edict of the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or (2) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or members of this website.

## Third Party Privacy Policies

5210Challenge.org is not responsible for the privacy practices of third party affiliates. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these sites.

## Display of Personal Information

Only a member's user name, point score, and number of entries, will be provided to a member's selected business, school, or organization. **Individual member information other than the point score and number of entries is private and not displayed publicly, shared with other members, or provided to any third parties or sponsors.**

Personal information (i.e. name, address, city, state, postal code, phone number, and e-mail) collected when members register are used to identify members and provide rewards when available, and are never disclosed to third parties.

**We do not share any personal information of children** who may be members either through a parent's account or their own personal account with anyone. Information that is gathered from children, as a parent or child tracks their data, is provided only to parents (for children 11 years old or less), and in cases of a "classroom membership", only a child's user name, points score, and number of entries are displayed on a team page for the teacher and other students in that class to view.

## Security

5210Challenge.org implements and maintains reasonable security measures and practices to protect all personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. These procedures apply to the collection and storage of personal data, as well as in instances where such data is provided to third-parties mentioned above.

Members who wish to stop their membership may delete their account by selecting the My Profile tab and clicking "Delete my Account" at the bottom of the page. All data associated with the account will be removed and cannot be retrieved.

If you have any further questions about our privacy policy or have suggestions on how it may be improved, please contact us.

5210Challenge.org notifies its visitors and members of material changes to the policy by providing a last update date, which also serves as the effective date, listed below.

**Last updated 3/25/2014**
